colorware.com 2016-12-14

# ColorWare About

  * welcome
  * contact us
  * history
  * awards
  * now in color
  * notable clients
  * x2 coating
  * press
  * social
  * privacy policy

### Welcome to ColorWare

ColorWare was founded on the idea that electronic devices could be more appealing than the standard colors offered by the original manufacturer. ColorWare products are creative and fashionable, giving their customers something unique that sets them apart from all the rest.

ColorWare is the only company in the world where you can create your own bespoke electronic device. The range of products spans from headphones to computers, portable PC’s, phones and gaming consoles. 

At ColorWare, quality control is rigorous. Great care is taken throughout every step of the process to ensure the highest level of quality from start to finish. Each ColorWare product is disassembled by hand from the original manufacturer. Once the product is disassembled, all parts are compartmentalized. Then the product is hand sprayed with a base coat. Once painted, It is baked at a low temperature to ensure the item dries thoroughly and evenly. Finally, the product is given an X2 coating that is also hand sprayed. This coating is a proprietary, scratch resistant, liquid plastic. The product is again baked, then polished and detailed and sent back to the production area for reassembly. 

Not only is the process durable and unique, but each step is completed at the ColorWare facility in Winona, Minnesota. 

### Timeline

2000

  * ColorWare was founded
  * Co-developed gaming consoles and PC's with AlienWare

2001

  * Expanded operations in Miami, Florida with AlienWare

2002

  * Launched website for online retail

2003

  * Returned to Minnesota, launched their first Apple products: iPod, iBook, PowerBook
  * The T.V. show, Screen Saver Launch, reviewed custom gaming consoles

2004

  * First Corporate Branding project with Jaguar featured an iPod

2005

  * First “Color Week” - ColorWare offers 25 colors
  * First Blackberry phone offered

2006

  * First retail agreement with Target.com
  * Retail agreement with Sam Goody
  * First iPhone offered

2007

  * First design studio introduced
  * ColorWare executives interview on National Television
  * Noted in Inc. 500’s list of fastest growing, privately held companies

2008

  * Second “Color Week” - added 6 colors
  * Launched the Stealth iPhone
  * Added 19 new products
  * Added digital art application
  * Added a machine shop

2009

  * Created first limited edition Stealth MacBook Pro
  * Third “Color Week” - 11 colors added
  * Launched Beats by Dr. Dre headphones
  * Doctors Without Borders auction: Custom Beatles rock band console

2010

  * Added HDTV, Segways and Dyson Air Multipliers
  * Launched ColorWare custom Grip for iPad

2011

  * Launched ColorWare custom Wedge
  * Added a Soft Goods category
  * Partnered with SOL REPUBLIC and Sennheiser
  * Offered Limited Edition Chrome Beats by Dre
  * Obtained the rights to ColorWare.com

2012

  * Expanded and quadrupled the size of their facility
  * Added a clean room for art application
  * Offered Special Edition Illusion Beats by Dr. Dre

2013

  * Launched two limited edition products including the KitchenAid mixer and Shred Beats Pro headphones
  * Expanded facility and built a state of the art machine shop
  * Fourth "ColorWeek" - 12 colors added
  * Partnered with Sennheiser
  * Updated website
  * ColorWare brought back the "Send In" option

2014

  * Launched the Now in Color Blog
  * Added laser engraving to products
  * Launched ColorWare Limited Sennheiser HD 800 G
  * Launched ColorWare Limited MacBook Air Retro
  * Partnership with Bose; launched Bose QC 25 headphones

2015

  * Launched ColorWare Limited 24k Gold Controllers
  * Launched ColorWare Limited Sennheiser HD800 C
  * Introduced patterns for the iPhone
  * Launched ColorWare Limited iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus Retro

### Our History

The idea of creating custom-made, on-demand electronic devices was developed in 1998 by CEO Justin Cisewski. With the help of his family members, the process of customizing different consumer electronics was perfected, and in 2000, ColorWare was founded.

From their humble beginnings, the Cisewski family began testing different paint finishes on computers and cellphones, while working out of a small warehouse. They focused all their attention on a few select products so they could perfect each step, from disassembly to painting and reassembly. Because the business was based on high quality customization standards, customers knew they could trust ColorWare and the business began to grow exponentially.

In 2000, ColorWare contacted Alienware and began painting gaming consoles and PC’s for them. Before long the Minnesota-based company moved to Miami, Florida to work with Alienware. The partnership lasted about two years before the Cisewski family decided to take their business back home to Minnesota. The Cisewski’s believed wholeheartedly in their business and they wanted to be free to experiment with other product offerings, paint coatings, and art applications.

In Minnesota, ColorWare began to add new products, new colors, and new departments to their company. They landed prominent retail promotions with Target and Sam Goody. Soon, ColorWare was a recognized name; checking in at number 108 on the list for fastest growing companies in Inc. 500. 

In 2008, a machine shop was added to the business. The machine shop created fixtures to support the customization process. And later, ColorWare began creating original custom products including, the Grip for iPad, and the Wedge, a stand for tablet PC’s.

In 2012, ColorWare quadrupled the size of their state-of-the-art paint facility. A clean room was also constructed to provide up-to-date art application processes. Currently, ColorWare provides colorization for more than 30 products and continues to build a ColorWare custom line of products uniquely their own. 

### Inc. 500

ColorWare was featured as number 108 on the Inc. 500 list of fastest growing privately held companies in the fall of 2007.

### Blog—Now In Color

Hello, and welcome to ColorWare’s new blog—Now In Color. ColorWare is a tech-savvy, fashion-minded brand that offers a unique customization service on a variety of tech products. Because of our intriguing art application processes, high quality photographs and videos, as well as our unique products and services, we designed Now In Color with more stimulating content. We have a dedicated team with diverse backgrounds to bring you credible and insightful information. Now In Color includes a comprehensive range of culturally relevant content such as tech, art, design, automobiles, sports, fashion and travel. 

### Notable Clients

ColorWare has had the pleasure of building partnerships and branding products for some of the most distinguished companies in the world.

  * SOL Republic
  * Sennheiser
  * Beats by Dre
  * Microsoft
  * Vitamin Water
  * Nike
  * Jaguar
  * Porsche
  * J. Crew
  * Bamford & Sons
  * Lacoste
  * Yahoo
  * National Geographic
  * Mountain Dew
  * MTV
  * IBM
  * Warner Bros
  * Peterbilt
  * W Hotels
  * Hyatt Hotels
  * Skull Candy
  * Colette
  * Reach Air Medical
  * WordPress
  * EA Sports
  * Charlotte Bobcats
  * Red Bull
  * Ping
  * Roc Nation
  * Square Enix

### X2 Coating

The X2 coating is the final step in our proprietary coatings process. It is a layer of clear coat, or urethane that protects the product from the environment. This coating is much like the finish on an automobile, impervious to minor scratches, water, and UV rays from the sun.

To achieve this highly durable finish, the X2 coating is applied similarly to the primer and base coat process. The urethane is hand sprayed in a controlled environment providing healthy, clean air with a full downdraft ventilation system in each booth. The clear coat, like the paint, is cured before assembly. 

### Press

Press Request Form

ColorWare has been featured in a variety of magazines. If you would like more information about featuring a ColorWare product in your magazine, please fill out our Press Request Form.

### [martha stewart weddings](https://dq5eb43zrmc0c.cloudfront.net/images/company/press/martha%20stewart%20weddings/inside-large.jpg)

Winter 2014

The Planner

Apple Wireless Keyboard

### [departures](https://dq5eb43zrmc0c.cloudfront.net/images/company/press/departures/inside-large.jpg)

November/December 2012

Newthink

Leica D-Lux 5 Camera

### [fitness](https://dq5eb43zrmc0c.cloudfront.net/images/company/press/fitness/nov-inside-large.jpg)

November/December 2012

Season's Tweetings

Apple Wireless Keyboard

### Social Media

For up-to-date news, product images, videos, and interactive posts tune into the following ColorWare social media sites: 

### Privacy Policy

ColorWare, Inc. Website Privacy Statement

This document was last updated on November 28, 2007.

##### 1\. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

ColorWare, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing [www.colorware.com](https://www.colorware.com/), you acknowledge and fully understand ColorWare, Inc.’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement. 

##### 2\. PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in ColorWare, Inc. services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties. 

##### 3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

ColorWare, Inc. collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server Logs, Use of Cookies, and Personal Information Users. 

##### a. Web Server Logs.

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

  * Your Internet protocol address.
  * The kind of browser or computer you use. 
  * Number of links you click within the site. 
  * State or country from which you accessed the site. 
  * Date and time of your visit. 
  * Name of your Internet service provider. 
  * Web page you linked to our site from. 
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

##### b. Use of Cookies

ColorWare, Inc. may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. 

ColorWare, Inc. reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

##### c. Personal Information Users

Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To fulfill your service requests for services.
  * To protect ourselves from liability,
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

##### 5\. ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant: [sales@colorware.com](mailto:sales@colorware.com).

##### 6\. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

ColorWare, Inc. has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

##### 7\. CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at [sales@colorware.com](mailto:sales@colorware.com).

You may also send your comments to:

ColorWare, Inc.

Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel

2050 W. 4th Street

Winona, MN 55987

ColorWare, Inc. will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.

### Holiday Order Datesshow

To ensure delivery before December 25th please order by the following dates.

  * ##### Send In

November

28

  * ##### Brand New

December

5

  * ##### Skins

December

15

**RUSH** orders are not affected by this chart. They will ship according to the rush option chosen.

Skins ordered with a device must be ordered by the Brand New cutoff to ensure December 25th delivery.
